{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "1. Which of the following is the paragraph tag in HTML?",
      "options": ["<p>", "<b>", "// <pre>", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "<p>"
    },
    {
      "question": " 2. Which of the following HTML attribute is used to define inline styles? ",
      "options": ["style ", "type", "class", "All of the above"], 
      "answer": "style"
    },

    {
      "question": " 3. HTML stands for?",
      "options": ["HighText Machine Language", 
      "HyperText and links Markup Language", 
      "HyperText Markup Language",
       "None of these"],
      "answer": "HyperText Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "question": " 4. The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is ---",
      "options": [
        "Head, Title, HTML, body",
        "HTML, Body, Title, Head ",
        "HTML, Links, Title, Body",
        "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
      ],
      "answer": "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
      "options": [
        "<pre>",
        "<a>",
        "<b>",
        "<br>"
      ],
      "answer": "<b>"
    },
    {
      "question": "6. Which of the following tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
      "options": ["<h3>", "<h1>", "<h5>", "<h6>"],
      "answer": "<h1>"
    },
    {
      "question": "7. Which character is used to represent the closing of a tag in HTML?",
      "options": ["/", "!", ".", "*"],
      "answer": "/"
    },
    {
      "question": "8. <input> is -",
      "options": ["a format tag", "an empty tag", "All of the above", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "an empty tag."
    },
    {
      "question": "9. The <hr> tag in HTML is used for -",
      "options": [
        "new line",
        "vertical ruler",
        "new paragraph",
        "horizontal ruler"
      ],
      "answer": "horizontal ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 .Which of the following attribute is used to provide a unique name to an element?",
      "options": ["class", "id", "type", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "id"
    }
  ]
}
